// Answer text must be under 25 characters otherwise they'll be truncated
// Answer value but be the lowercase LETTER of the correct answer (a, b, c, or d)
// All games must be 10 questions - do not delete any!
module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What is the average radius around a hive that bees will forge for food?', 
      a: '2 miles', 
      b: '200 yards',
      c: '20 yards',
      d: '2 yards',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What\'s the average lifespan of a worker bee?', 
      a: '5-6 years', 
      b: '5-6 months',
      c: '5-6 weeks',
      d: '5-6 days',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'What\'s the average lifespan of the queen bee?', 
      a: '2-3 years', 
      b: '2-3 months',
      c: '2-3 weeks',
      d: '2-3 days',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What percent of bees in the hive are male?', 
      a: '50%', 
      b: '30%',
      c: '10%',
      d: '5%',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'The male bees are called drones. Other than mating with the queen, what is their job?', 
      a: 'To guard the hive', 
      b: 'Collect pollen and nectar',
      c: 'Remove dead bees',
      d: 'Nothing',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'How often does the queen mate?', 
      a: 'Once in her life', 
      b: 'Yearly',
      c: 'Every lunar cycle',
      d: 'Daily',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'At the end of the summer, if the queen doesn\'t need to mate, what happens to the male bees (drones).', 
      a: 'They become female', 
      b: 'Winterize the hive',
      c: 'Get kicked out',
      d: 'Join another hive',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'The queen can lay as many as _____ eggs a day', 
      a: '5,000', 
      b: '2,500',
      c: '500',
      d: '25',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Bees communicate to each other through pheromones and _______', 
      a: 'Dancing', 
      b: 'Grooming',
      c: 'Ultrasonic chirps',
      d: 'Rapid wing movement',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is honey?', 
      a: 'Bee poop', 
      b: 'Bee vomit',
      c: 'Bee blood',
      d: 'Bee\'s knees',
      answer: 'b'
    }
  ]
};